Preliminary Guide to the Luther Brady papers, MS2147.UA
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- UP0005 (Box 5)
  - Chemo, Bone Marrow, etc., Phillips, Wasserman et al, April 1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Brady, L.W.: Radiation Induced Sarcomas (Int. Skeletal Soc.), October 1978 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Deposits, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Jama article "Therapeutic Radiology" - Drs. J. delRegat & L.W. Brady (Modern Radiation Onc.), June 5, 1981 - Vol. 245, No. 21 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Personal, undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Pion Radiotherapy Progral, April 1981 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Radiation Sensitizers & Rad. Protectors Comb. with Rad. Ther., Baden, Austria, May (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Brady - Biologic basis for Combined Modality Treatment for Cancer, Ruvelson Lecture, October 12, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Mycosis Fungoides - Drs. Micaily, Brady, Voderheid, Philadelphia Medicine, July 6, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - "Innovations in Clinical Radiation Therapy Research" by L.W. Brady, sent to Raven Press, June 16, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Ca of the Stomach - Present Status, Phila Medicine, April 4, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Misc. Corres. (Manuscript), undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Curative Rad. Ther. Ca. of Breast "Contemporary Surgery" Brady, Graeffe, Glassburn, etc., January 13, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Nuclear Bone Scintigraphy & Gallium Imagin in Assessment of Post-Prosthetic Implant...LaManna, etc., July 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - An Unusual Cause of "Hot Nose" - LaManna, Micaily, LWB, Hoover, July 1982 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Implications of Lymphoscintigraphy in Oncologic Practice:..Croll, Brady, Dadparvar, July 1, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Frontiers in Rad. Ther & Oncol., Radiotherapy for carcinoma of the br. instead of mastec. - an update, Prosnitz, et al, April 7, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Brady, cancer of the Vagina (McGowan's book), undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Vaginal Neoplasia, undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Application of the Autofluoroscope to Cerebral Blood Flow Studies, undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Torpie-Bereavement: Its Source in Hospital Death, undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Torpie - Bereavement: Its Sources in Hospital Death, undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Conray et al., Bleomycin and Methotrexate, undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Stanton - Changing Approaches to Physics Teaching of Radiologists, undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Clinical Uses of Bone Scanning - Brady and Croll, undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Brady: Current Concept in ca. Surgery or Rad. Rx., December 1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Brady = Multi Modality Therapy (For Brodsky's Book, Grune and Stratton), undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Lessig-Croll-Brady - Primary Splenic Tumor Diagnosed by Preop Sulfur Colloid Scan, undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Trends in Dx & Rx Tumors, CNS AOM, November 9, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - LWB-Manning: Radiation Therapy in Primary Ca of the Ureter, undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - [Untitled], undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Croll et all - The Use of Radionucles in the Diagnosis of Tumors of Central Nervous System, undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Carcinoma of the Vagina, Lewis and Brady, undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Radiation Review - First Draft, undated (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Brady - Ionizing Radiation A Double-Edged Sword, Transactions of the College of Physicians, December 1976 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Brady - Is there a Need for a Diagnostic-Oncoradiologist? Applied Radiology, undated (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Brady - Combined Modality Therapy of Gyn. Cancer, undated (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Inhibition of AKR Leukemi, L.W. Brady MD, undated (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Improving Results for the Treatment of Endometrial Ca., undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Asbell, Gado, Saluk, Vonderheid, Brady, Mycosis Fungoides, undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Brady - Cancer of the Ovary (Gilbert-Kagan), undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
- UP0006 (Box 6)
  - Maliginant Intraocular Tumors - L.W. Braady, Shields Augsburger, Day, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Dr. Kappula, Malignant Intraocular Tumors, January Lecture, ARS, April 30, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Patient Reports, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Changing Role of Rad. Onc. in Ca Man. LWB. March/April 1983, Vol. 33, No. 2. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - [Unlabeled], undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Commentaries on: Mesothelioma & Malignant Melanoma to Harvey Gilbert, March 11, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Practical Clinical Radiation Ther. A.M. Markoe's chapter for Dr. S. Benham Kahn's Textbook, undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Combined Mod. Dose Elec. Beam Rdi. & Topical Chemo. Cutaneous T- Cell Lymphoma, Micaily, Bonderheid, Brady, 10/6/82 IJBO, October 6, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Radiation Therapy for Malignant Intraocular Tumors (for Dr. Gonzalez's book on eye) by Brady, Shields, Augsburger, Day, Markoe, Castro & Suit, July 1, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Chapter "The Role of Radiation Therapy in Tumors of the Eye" for book New Directions in Therapeutic Radiology by Carl Mansfield - Correspondence, November 1984 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - JAMA's CONTEMPO '84 - Progress in Radiation Oncology - by Drs. del Regato, Brady, Sheline, January 25, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Combined Mod. Dose Elec. Beam Radio & Topical Chemo. Cutaneous T-Cell Lymphoma, Micaily, Vonderheid, Brad (IJRO), October 6, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - The Changing Role of Radiation Onc. In Ca Managment - for ACS for CA - Mar./Apr. 1983, by Dr. Brady, March/April 1983 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Cnacers "The Changing Roll of Rad. Onc. in Ca Man. M.S., June 1983 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Spanish Translation of "Radiation Therapy as Primary Trtmt. for Ca of the Breast" by Drs. Brady, Bedwinek, Loughead (translated by Dr. Gisela Cisneros) 8/84 and Chapter 11: The Changing Role of Radiotherapy" by Dr. Brady and Bedwinek (Dr. Bonadonna's book), August 1984 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Treatment of Orbital Pseudo tumors and Lymphoma, Drs. Barthold, Harvey, Markoe, Brady, Augsburger, Shields (Ars/S.F. Mtg.), October 22, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "The R.T.O.G. - 1987" To Dr. Rubin 2/19/88 for IJRO (based on ASTRO speech), February 19, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - 1987 ASTRO GOld Medal Paper (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - For RSNA -- 11/84: A.M. Markoe "Radioactive Eyeplaque Therapy vs. Enucleation for the Treatment of Post. Uveal Malignant Melanomas," Markoe, Brady, Shields, Augsberger, Micaily, Damsker, Day, November 1984 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Carcinoma of the Larynx: Glottis--Brady, Micaily, Markoe, Damsker for Dr. Romanini, January 17, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Radiotherapy Trials in H/N Cancer - Venice 10/19-21/83, LWB, Marcial, Davis, Laramore, Kramer (Dr. Bonadonna's Book), October 19-21, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - "The Use of Multiple Plaque Therapy in Management of Malignant Intraocular Tumors" by Drs. Anthony Berson, LWB, (review by Shields, Augsbur.), September 1983 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - 90 Strontium Beta Irradiation of Glaucoma Filtering procedures, by Drs. Berkowitz, Spaeth, and Brady (abstract Wills Eye & HU), 1983 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - "Carcinoma of the Kidney" done for Dr. Maguire by Dr. Brady, October 3, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Split - Course Radiotherapy of Carcinoma of the Urinary Bladder Stages C and D (RTOC Study) by Drs. Marcial, Amato, Brady, Johnson, Martz, Hanley (to be published IJRO), May 20, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - "Clinical Risk Factors in Posterior Uveal Malignant Melanoma: to be publi. IJRO by Drs. Augsburger, Gamel, Sardi, Greenburg, Shields, Donoso, Markoe, Brady, Dav., June 1985 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Los Angeles, September 19-22, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Spinal Cord Mets, undated (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Caesar's A.C. Symposium "Management Chronic Pain Syndrome: Primer for Phys.", March 23-25, 1981 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Radiation Ther. for the Managment of cancer Pain - sent to Cointuing Education (HMCH), May 10, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Contempo - 1985 for JAMA "Radiation Oncology" by Brady, Davis & del Regato (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Chapter 13: "Computer Tomography in Radiation Therapy" by Drs. Brady, Davis & Yaeger for Gonzalez book --Head & Spine Imaging, undated (Box 6, Folder 32)
- UP0007 (Box 7)
  - Cancer of the Breast: Treatment Today, L.W. Brady MD, undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Diagnostic Significance of Cerebral Blood Flow Studies in Cerebral Occlusive Disease, undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Markoe-Saluk: Combined Effects of Rx. and Chemo., undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Wallner, R.J. et al., Color Vision, Perception & Color Scanning, undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Check et al. Differences in the Protective Effect of Completee Freund's Adjuvant..., undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Check et al Differences in the Protective Effect of Complete Freund's Adjuvant in Spontaneous Versus Transplanted Lymphomas in AKR Mice, undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Educational and Training Needs for Radiation Therapists, undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Check et al Effect of Complete Freund's Adjuvant on Transplanted & Spontaneous Lymphoma in AKR MIce, undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Check et al. Effect of Radiation Therapy on Mups Delayed Type Hypersensitivity, undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Brady-Markoe - Effect of Sub-lethal X-irradiation of erythropoiesis in the mouse, undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Stanton and Brady, Encyclopedia Britannica, Electron Radiography, undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Brady - Cancer of the Vulva (McGowan's book), undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Stanton - Physical Measurements of the Electron Radiography System, undated (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - ERG Papers, undated (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Stanton et al. Electron Radiography - A New X-ray Imaging System "Applied Radiology", undated (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Markoe et al - Elevated Serum Iga Level in Cancer Patients Int. J. of Radiation ONcology, undated (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Seminars in Oncology, Head & Neck Cancer - Dr. B., Guest Editor, undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Prostate Cancer: LWB Chapter for Dr. Heliman Book, July 1989 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - "Combined Radiotherapy & Chemo. in Gynecologic Oncology" in Final Revision of ICTRO Gynecology Paper, tobe published in IJRO, September 1987 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Thoracic Irradiation with or without Levamisole in Unresectable Non-Small Cell Carcinoma of the Lung: A Phase II Randomized Trial of RTOG - Perez, Bauer, Wasserman, Byhardt, LWB, Doggett, etc. To Be considered by IJRO, December 1987 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Patients, undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - "Complications from Radiation Therapy to the Eye" - LWB, undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - "The Radiation Therapy Oncology Group: An Outline of Clinical Research Activities" - LWB, Kramer, Wasserman, Keiser, Davis, Pajak, Cox, Griffin, Perez, Phillips, Rubin, Seydel: IJROBP; Stutus Report for ICTRO Document, November 1987 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - "Compensated" Split-Course vs Continuous Rad. Ther. of Carcinoma of the Tonsillar Fossa: Final Results of a Prospective Randomized Clin. Trial of RTOG- Marcial, Scott, Rotman, LWB, etc. to be published, February 1988 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Second Malignancies in Patients Who Have Head & NEck Cancers: Incidence, Effect on Survival & Implications for Chemoprevention Based on RTOG Experience by Cooper, Pajak, Rubin, Tupchong, LWB, etc. To be published 5/88, May 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Local/Regional Control, ACS Conf - l.A> for Diane Fink "Cancer", undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - "Radiation Cataract Removal in Patients Treated for Retinoblastoma" - H. Logan Brooks, Nelson, Shields, Augsburger, Markoe, LWB (7/88) to be published in AMA, July 1988 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Gynecologic Oncology - 2nd Edition, Malcom Coppleson, MD, Monaghan, Morrow, Tattersall - co-authors; Dr. b. to rewrite chapter due 12/88, December 1988 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - The Treatment of Gastrointestinal Cacner Using Monoclonal Antibodies," Markoe, LWB, Amendola, Karlsson, Fisher, Micaily, Rackover, Woo, Bulova, Steplewski, Koprowski, San Francisco Symp. (Vaeth) Leukophresis 17-1A paper, "Frontiers in Oncology," Vol. 24 Basel, Switzerland, February 1989 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - "Future Prospects in RT in Gyn Oncology" - Coppleson, September 1989 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- UP0008 (Box 8)
  - Article Reprints, circa 1965-1997 (Box 8, Loose-material 1)
- UP0009 (Box 9)
  - Brady - Carcinoma of the Ovary (with J. Blessing), December 1978 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Glassburn-Brady: Hyperbaric Oxygen in Radiation Therapy Cancer for Springer-Verlag - due August 1976 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Glassburn - Indications for Lymph Node Scanning Utilizing Colloidal Gold 198, undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Honda-Clinical Use of Limulus Endotoxin Detections Test for Short-Lived Radiopharm., undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Wasllner et al "Combined Chemotherapy and External Irradiation in Management of Acute Leukemia", undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Correlation of 198 AU Abdominal Lymph Scans with Lymphangiograms & Lymph Node Biopsy, undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Sophie Check, undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Biodistribution and Pharmacokinetics (Pancreatic Tumor Models, Arnold Markoe, 24th Meeting-Nuclear Medicine Society, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Glassburn-Hyperbaric Oxygen, April 1976 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Brady - The Role of Bone Scanning in the Cancer Patient, September 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Brady - Bone Scanning, undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Croll-Brady-Wallner-Honda, New Techniques in Tumor Localization and Radioimmunoassay, undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Brady et al - Evolution of Radiotherapeutic Techniques, undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Hyperbaric Oxygen with Chemotherapy and radiation therapy in Cancer, undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - M.J. Solan "Radiation Therapy for Gyn Malignancies"" Shingleton Book, August 1988 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - "Radiation Oncology for Gynecologic Malignancies " MJ Solan, LWB -- Cptr. for Shingleton's Gyn. Onc.: Curr Diag & Trtmt, July 1994 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - 1986 Ellis Berven Lectureship -- ACT Radiologica, "cancer Cure with ORgan Preservation Using Radiation Therapy," LWB, Markoe, Fisher & MIcaily, August 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Prefact on Brachytherapy for book - High Dose Rate Afterloading Techniques by Prof. Helmut Vahrson, November 25, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - 1987 Astro Gold Medal Lectureship, Boston, MA, October 20, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Replace "Primary Introcular Malignancy" - Brady/Markoe/Del Regato Issue, undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Hyperthermia: The Development of Management Fees, LWB (7/1/87) Journal of Radiology RSNA, July 1, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Radiation Therapy of Urologic Cancer - Barthold & Brady, June 1987 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - "Rad. Ther. & Hyperthermia" LWB & Heinrich S., Contempo- AMA, July 1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Role of Distant Metastasis as a Site of Failure in Cancers of the Head & Neck Region --Drs. John Del Rowe, Pajak, Davis, LWB, Mohiuddin, Rubin, Marcial, Stetz-RTOG, November 1986 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Protocolos Terapeuticos Del Cancer De La Clinica Universitaria De Navarra, Editor, Beatriz E. Amendola, MD, Co-Authro, Dr. Brugenblass, June 1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - MABs for Use in Radiotherapy and Diagnosis, 2/2/87 to Fran Glica, February 2, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - MAD in Dx. & Treatment of Ca. for Dr. Bleehen, April 1987 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - MAB In Diagnosis & Treatment of Cancer, L.W.B. - London Bogat Coll. Radiologists, February 16, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Therapeutic and Diagnostic Uses of Modified Monoclonal Antibodies, LWB, Woo, Heindel, Markoe, C. Koprowski, H. Koprowski, Mattis, June 19, 986 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Monoclomnal Antibody backup material, undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Combined Radiotherapy & Chemotherapy in Gyn. Oncology to PHillips & Rubin, May 1987 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Treatment of Advanced and Recurrent Gyn. cancer, Cancer, May 1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - "Modern Brachytherapy" text by B. Pierquin, J.F. Wilson, D. Chassagne; Preface by LWB Masson Publishing, Paris, January 1987 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - "Clinical Treatment Planning in Gyn Cancer" for Dr. Veeth (sent 7/86), July 1986 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Seminars in Oncology, Vol. XV, No. 1, February 1988 "Head & Neck Cancer," J. Yarbro, Bornstein, Mastrangelo, Eds. (LWB, Blitzer, Zarbo, Crissman, Snow, David, Marcial, Pajak, Kramer, Stetz, etc. (Box 9, Folder 26)
- UP0010 (Box 10)
  - Duplicate Articles and Book Chapters, undated (Box 10, Loose-material 1)
- UP0011 (Box 11)
  - Radiation Therapy for Malignant Tumors of the Eye --LWB, Shields, Augsburger, Markoe, Day, Karlson chapter for Dr. Carl Mansfield's book, June 20, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Corres., undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Radiation Therapy for Malignant Tumors of the Eye--Drs. Brady, Shields, Augsburger, Markoe, Day, Karlsson (Dr. Mansfield's Book), May 5, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - "Clinical Treatment Planning in Gynecologic Cancer, for Dr. Jerome Vaeth, West Coast Cancer FCoundation, May 16, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - RSNA Presidential, "Organ Preservation", November 1985 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - RSNA - Presidential Address (originals), October 1985 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Cancer Cure with Organ Preservation using Radiation Therapy, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Clinical Implications of Imm. Pheno in Cutaneous T-Call Lymphoma, B. Micaily, undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - 'Failure Patterns in GYN Cancer" from Rome mtg 4/85 - sent to Rubin 9/85, September 1985 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "Ca. of Breast" West Coast Cancer Fdn., March 1986 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Presidential Address, Radiological Society of North America, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Radiation Therapy for Brain Metastasis--Glenn E. Sheline & LWB (for journal Neuro-Oncology), September 25, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Eye Plague Paper, Original Graphs for Markoe-Brady paper, Vienna, March 1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - "Ca of the Breast: A Historical Perspective" (Sent 6/85 to Romanini), June 1985 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Challenge of Local Control & Impact on Survival. to Rubin 9/23/85 from Rome Conf. 4/85, September 23, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Conservation Surger @ Curative R RX in Ca of the Breast (to Romanini 6/5/85), June 5, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Radiation Therapy in Elderly Patient - Vaeth Book, August 1985 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Ocular Disease - Dr. Markoe for Astro syllabus & book chapter, August 1985 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - "Conservative Surgery & Curative Radiation Therapy in Cancer of the Breast." sent to Jerry Vaeth, June 10, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - 125Iodine Implantation...in early ca of prostate - G. Giles, January 1986 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Radition Oncology: Programs for the Present and Future, June 14, 1984 (Box 11, Loose-material 1)
  - Radioactive Eyplaque Therapy Versus Enucleation for the Treatment of Posterior Uveal Malignant Melanomas, 4/30/85 submitted in final form to Radiology, April 30, 1985 (Box 11, Loose-material 2)
  - Radiation Oncology - ACS '84, Brady/Markoe Cancer, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Radiation Oncology: Programs for the Present and Future by Brady & Sheline (6/13/1984) for ACS National Convention, S.F., Cal., June 13, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Modern Brachytherapy by Drs. B. Pierquin, J. Frank Wilson, Daniell Chassagne--Prefact by LWB, Massen Publishing USA, January 1987 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- UP0012 (Box 12)
  - "The Natural History of Benign Prostatic Hyperplasia," G. Mieszkalski, J. Keit, LWB (3/93 to Z. Petrovich, MD), March 1993 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - "The Biologic Basis of Radiation Ther." Glenn Mieszkalski, for ACS publications, May 1993 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Plaque Radiotherapy of Uveal Melanoma, Shields, Shields, DePotter, Hernandez, Brad. Submitted: '93 Int. Ophth. Cl. Ed., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Radiotherapy of Ocular Tumors - Hernandez JC, Brady LW< Shields JA, Shields CL, DePotter, P., undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Choroidal Melanoma: LWB chapter for Dr. Heilmann book, July 1989 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - LWB Co-Author with Michael Giblin, M.D., presentations: Episcleral Plaque Radiotherapy for Uveal Melanoma & for Retinoblastom, Drs. Shields & Augsberger, June 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Reasons for Enucleation Following Plaque Radiotherapy for Posterior Uveal Melanoma: clin. Findings" Carol Shields, MD, J. Shileds, U. Karlsson, Markoe, LWB, August 1988 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Recurrence of Post. Uveal Melanoma & Patient Survival after 60 Co Episcleral Plaque Therapy." UK, Augsburger, Shiels, Markoe, LWB, Woodleigh, October 1988 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - "Enucleation Following Plaque Radiotherapy for Post. Uveal Melanoma: Histopathologic Findings" 10/88, Carol Shields, J. Shields, R. Eagle, Karlsson, Markoe, LWB., October 1988 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - "The Treatment of Primary Intraocular Malignancy," LWB, Markoe, Amendola, Karlsson, Micaily, Shields, Augsburger, IJRO (7/88) del Regato's festschrift, July 1988 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - "The Treatment of Choroidal Melanoma by Plaque Brachytherapy," by J.C. Hernandez, LWB< J. Shields, C. Shields, November 1990 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Low Doese ocular irradiation for choroidal hemangiomas associated with nonhegmatogenous retinal detachment," Todd Scott, Augsburger, LWB, C. Hernandez, R. Woodleigh, February 1991 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - "Impact of Local Tumor Relapse Following Cobalt-60 Plque Radiotherapy on Patient Survival." Tamara Vrabec, J. Augsburger, J. Gamel, LWB, Hernandez, February 1991 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - "Brachytherapy of Choroidal Melanomas," LWB/C Hernandez, Md editorial for Prof. Rolf Sauer's Journal, Erlangen, Germany, June 1991 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - "Primary Intraocular Malignancy" Brady/Markoe Del Regato Issue, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - "Indium-111 Labeled Anti-EGFr-425 Scintigraphy in the Detection of Malig. Gliomas" - Dadparvar, Krishna, Miyamoto, LWB< Brown, Woo, Bender, Slizofski, Eshleman Chevres, November 1992 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - "Treatment of nonresectable malignant iris tumors with custom designed plaque radiotherapy," Carol Shields, j. shields, Patrick De Potter MD, Arun D. Signh, MD, Carlos Hernandez MD, LWB, November 1993 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - "Plaque Radiotherapy in the Mgmt. of Juxtapapillary Choroidal Melanoma" by Patrick DePotter MD, Shieldses, Cater, Hernandez, LWB - Archives of Ophthalm., June 1993 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - "Ophthalmic Plaque Radiotherapy in Primary Choroidal Melanoma" - Z. Petrovich, G. Luxton, JA Shields, CL Shields, LWB (1991 or 1992) (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - "Tumors of the Adrenal Gland" for Principles and Practice of Radiation Oncology - LWB, 2nd Edition, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - "Radiation Cures Cancer," LWB & Mary Ella Sanders for ACRO, February 1993 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - "Therapeutic Advances in Radiologic Treatment of Cancer" - LWB< Micaily, Miyamoto, Reaid, Mieszkalski; Cancer Supplement, 12/1/1993, Vol. 72 No. 11 (10/93), December 1, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - "Cancer of the Fallopian Tube" by D. M. Ostapovitz, MD & LWB - 10/21/94 (Helmut Vahrson, MD, Giessen, Germany), October 21, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - "Initial Clin. Eval. of 125 I-Labeled Internalizing Antibody Chimeric 17-1A for Metastatic Colony Cancer" to be publi. Jrnl of Nuc. Med. (10/94) (new title); "A Phase I Trial of 125 I-Labeled Internalizing Antibody, Chimeric 17-1A" (orig. title), Ruby Meredith MD UAL-Birmingham, October 1994 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - [Unlabeled], December 1994 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - "Contemporary Indications for IORT," F. Asrari, B. Costleigh, B. Micaily, LWB, January 6, 1995 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - "EGFR-425 MAB with I-125 in the Adj. Trtmt of High Grade Astrocytomas" -- Lesley Snelling/Wistar/Neurosurg-HU, September 1994 (Box 12, Folder 27)